Maša Wu

+45 52600051 • info@masawudesign.dk • https://www.linkedin.com/in/masa-wu

OBJECTIVE

Seeking an UX/UI or Web Development position at a tech savvy company where my strong creativity, design, communication and management skills will help your company grow and deliver the right message to the target audience.

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

- Technology Savvy: Proficient with Adobe software: Photoshop CC, Illustrator CC, Adobe XD, Premier Pro CC, Animate CC, Dreamweaver CC, and Muse. Competent in HTML, CSS, JS, SQL and MS Office suite.
- Effective Communicator: Competent in writing, editing, and proofreading business documents. Skilled in verbal communication and generating business and creative content.
- Storyteller: Communicating information and facts through engaging content that builds up a strong brand with loyal and active audience.
- **Team Worker:** Demonstrated working efficiently in an international team environment. Experienced being a SCRUM master, guiding a team of people by managing tasks progress, using problem-solving techniques and iterating.
- Self-Starter: Independent and self-confident, willing to take initiative when needed. Promote positive outlook on upcoming projects and persistent to accomplish set goals on time in a fast-paced environment.
- Detail Oriented: Meticulous about details and double-checking the work. Delivering high quality work while effectively
 prioritizing projects and deadlines
- Problem Solver: Resolving day-to-day administrative and operational problems at various working environments

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

Freelance Web Designer ♦ USA & Slovenia.

(09/2016-Present)

Worked pro-bono for multiple clients based in the USA and Slovenia. Projects ranged from a portfolio website for a professional graphic designer, a business website for my current employer and a food blog for my personal interest. Received top level feedback from clients.

- Created my food blog with WordPress.org http://www.misschili.net/
- Designed a portfolio website for a San Francisco based graphic designer client http://www.sallyhuang.net/
- Building professional business website for a restaurant in San Francisco http://www.misschili.net/rtb/rtb.html
- Built a personal portfolio showcasing my recent projects: http://www.masawudesign.dk/kea/masawudesign

Executive Assistant ♦ KLIMER STIRN & CO. d.n.o., Domzale, Slovenia

(11/2012-Present)

Klimer is a leading Slovenian company specialized in clean room testing for the pharmaceutical industry with 16 employees. In 2012, I got promoted and became an executive assistant. Now I am responsible for: managing business partners' and customers' relationship, preparing various regulation compliances prior to testing projects and post-processing test result, overviewing of company's logistics, reporting fleet expenses, planning business events, and monitoring company's expenses.

- Communicating through verbal and written communication technology tools with local and international business partners
- Organizing meetings, planning international business trips, education seminars, and organizing team building events

Office Assistant ♦ KLIMER STIRN & CO. d.n.o., Domzale, Slovenia

(10/2008-11/2012)

When I started working at Klimer as Office assistant I performed variety of office tasks on employer's request. I helped them build a recognizable brand with a strong logo. Daily I was responsible for: typing documents and correspondences; entering and analyzing data; scanning, printing and copying; managing office supplies. If needed I was requested to help with event planning.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Kea Multimedia Design & Communication (expected 07/2019) • KEA Københavns Erhvervsakademi, KØBENHAVN, DENMARK Office Administration Specialist Certificate (05/2017) • CITY COLEGE OF SAN FRANCISCO, CA, USA Cosmetology High School Diploma (09/2014) • ZAVOD AI, Ljubljana, SLOVENIA Gymnasium High School Diploma (06/2008) • ŠCRM KAMNIK, Kamnik, SLOVENIA